[
  {
    "id":0,
    "question": "What element of voice is important in order to communicate effectively with others ?",
    "a": "Documentation",
    "b": "Vocabulary",
    "c": "Grammar",
    "d": "Articulation",
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "id":1,
    "question": "Often, the most effective way to interpret others' nonverbal cues is to look at their",
    "a": "clothing style.",
    "b": "leg movements.",
    "c": "facial expressions.",
    "d": "office decor.",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "id":2,
    "question": "Expressing empathy and being willing to help others are the aspects of emotional intelligence that relate to",
    "a": "self-management.",
    "b": "social awareness.",
    "c": "relationship management.",
    "d": "self-awareness.",
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id":3,
    "question": "All of the following are ma?or technology trends in e-commerce in 2013-2014 except",
    "a": "cloud computing enables the creation of big data.",
    "b": "apps create a new plat$orm for online marketing and commerce.",
    "c": "the mobile computing platform begins to rival the 5' platform.",
    "d": "real-time advertising becomes a reality with gains in computing power and speeds.",
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "id":4,
    "question": "Identify the option with the correct spelling.",
    "a": "paraphernalia",
    "b": "programme",
    "c": "pediatrics",
    "d": "beserk",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "id":5,
    "question": "There are three underlined words below, followed by their usages. Determine the sentences, in which the use of words is correct or appropriate : Pray. Prey. Prying  A. If you pray with faith, they say, it will be answered. B. He has fallen a prey to cheats C. Prying into the affairs of others is bad.",
    "a": "A and B",
    "b": "A and C",
    "c": "A, B and B",
    "d": "B and C",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "id":6,
    "question": "Choose the word closest in meaning to replace the word given in bold Portend : It appears to many that the US :War on terrorism” portends trouble in the gulf.",
    "a": "Introduces",
    "b": "evokes",
    "c": "spells",
    "d": "bodes",
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "id":7,
    "question": "Choose the word closest in meaning to replace the word given in bold. Ostensible: Manohar’s ostensible job was to guard the building at night.",
    "a": "apparent",
    "b": "blatant",
    "c": "Ostentatious",
    "d": "insidious",
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "id":8,
    "question": "what's the field of AI",
    "a": "Datamining",
    "b": "Algorithems",
    "c": "Data warehourse",
    "d": "Network",
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id":9,
    "question": "what's low level programming language",
    "a": "c#",
    "b": "php",
    "c": "html",
    "d": "assembly",
    "answer": "d"
  }
]